First, install the Visual Studio Extension
Open Visual Studio
Create a C# project
Query a valid License though Tools -> Hybridizer Configuration
Enter your email and click "Query License"
Check your mailbox and copy the license text to your clipboard (Ctrl-C)
Paste the license key in the appropriate text box and click Validate
Make sure your project builds in 64 bits (x64 configuration)
Implement some parallel code (Parallel.For or cuda-like loop)
And decorate the kernels with EntryPointAttribute
Right Click on your project -> Hybridize Project -> Generate
Add the appropriate using statements (Ctrl-;)
Build the .Net project in x64
Then the generated native project
You can now invoke the generated CUDA code using HybRunner
Executing the project logs that the native library has been mapped
and that the generated code has been properly invoked
Let's profile using Nsight
You can spot Nsight profiling the kernel you wrote in C#
Inspection of kernel launch gives you all the expected details.